https://www.adventuremedicalkits.com/privacy-policy/

We use cookies to give you the best online experience. By using our website you agree to our use of cookies in accordance with our
Cookie Policy.
Agree
Compare (0)
You have no items to compare.
Log In
Adventure Medical Kits Logo
Search:
Medical Kits
Professional SeriesMountain SeriesUltralight / WatertightSportsman SeriesAdventure First AidAdventure Dog SeriesMarineTravelPocket Size Kits
Trauma
QuikClotTrauma KitsTourniquets
Water Purifiers
Supplies
Kit Refills & AdditionsHygieneBlisterBurnEasy Access BandagesBen's Tick & Insect RepellentNatrapel Tick & Insect RepellentAfter BiteThe Itch Eraser
Medical Kits
Professional SeriesMountain SeriesUltralight / WatertightSportsman SeriesAdventure First AidAdventure Dog SeriesMarineTravelPocket Size Kits
Trauma
QuikClotTrauma KitsTourniquets
Water Purifiers
Supplies
Kit Refills & AdditionsHygieneBlisterBurnEasy Access BandagesBen's Tick & Insect RepellentNatrapel Tick & Insect RepellentAfter BiteThe Itch Eraser
Easy Access Bandages
Easy Care First AidGenuine First AidGenuine First Aid Red Cross
Privacy Policy
Adventure Ready Brands appreciates your interest in our products and company; your patronage at our retail partners and on-line; and your concern for privacy and security of personal information.
Adventure Ready Brands has updated its Privacy Policy ("Policy") as of May 25, 2018, which can be summarized with these 3 basic principles:
We do not sell data.
We use data only to enhance our relationship with you.
You are always welcome to contact us about your privacy, whether you have questions, wish to provide any feedback, or make changes.
This Policy applies when you access our websites and mobile applications, shop with retailers that sell Adventure Ready Brands products, contact us by phone, email, and chat or connect with us in any other manner, including in our social media channels.
European Union Residents
Adventure Ready Brands' US websites and social media outlets are intended for use only in the United States. Adventure Ready Brands' Canadian websites are intended for use only in Canada.
Use outside these countries is prohibited.
If you are a resident of the European Union, we require that you shop via our international retail partners and their websites where available.
If you wish to take advantage of any of your rights pursuant to the European Union Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as the Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the "Right to be Forgotten"), please contact us directly and we will be happy to assist you.
If you reside in the European Union, our websites may have collected your information from non-essential cookies.
Why We Collect Your Information
We collect information for many reasons such as:
process your order,
contact you about the status of your order,
send you tracking information for your packages,
reserve store inventory for you,
post your product review,
save your purchase history,
provide you with information about the products you've purchased (for example, in the case of a recall),
manage your online account (such as saving your wish list),
mail catalogs to you,
send you promotional emails, and
provide you with the best possible customer service.
The additional information that we receive from you and gather from other sources allows us to serve you better and improve the overall shopping experience for all of our customers. Such information helps to improve the design of our website, understand shopping preferences, serve advertisements that we think may be of interest to customers, and improve upon the content of our promotions and customer service.
Contact us, by phone, U.S. and Canada: (800) 258-4696
by phone from outside the U.S.: Access Code +1 (800) 258-4696
by email: cs@tendercorp.com
by mail: 944 Industrial Park Road, Littleton, NH, 03561.
Information We Collect
Information that you share with Adventure Ready Brands:
We collect and store the information that you provide to us. For example, you may provide information to us when you place an order or create an account on our websites, shop at our retail partners, apply for a job, enter a sweepstakes or contest, join our mailing list, take a survey, or connect with one of our customer service representatives. Types of information that you may provide to us include, for example: your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, payment information, date of birth or pictures. If you choose to share information on our social media sites, including the posting of any pictures, please read our Content Submission Terms and Conditions. You may also share information about a gift recipient if you purchase a gift card or send a package to someone other than yourself.
Additional information that we may receive:
We also collect and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via the internet. Types of information that we may gather through this automatic process include your device location, IP address, browsing history and purchase history. Please our read our Cookie Policy for additional information.
Sharing Your Information
Adventure Ready Brands is in the adventure, safety, and health-care business – not the business of selling data or personal information. Adventure Ready Brands does not ever sell its data and only shares information to the extent necessary to enhance our relationship with you and your relationship with us.
We have partners who help us with things such as fraud protection & investigation, shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, survey distribution, Adventure Ready Brands advertising across third-party platforms, promotions management, and payment processing.
We share your information with these providers only as needed so that they can perform those services on our behalf.
Some third parties, such as Facebook and Google, use the data to serve you ads that we think may interest you. These third parties may combine the information we share with them with information already in their possession; they may also offer you choices about which ads you see on their platforms.
Some third-party vendors use analytics data for a variety of purposes such as to improve the design and content of our websites, to help us learn which pages are most attractive to all of our visitors and what promotions visitors like to see, and to gauge the success of our advertising campaigns. One such vendor is Google Analytics. Please click here for more information about how data is collected and processed in connection with the Google Analytics service: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
We work closely with our partners to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected and require these third parties keep your personal information secure and confidential. We may allow some of our third-party partners to use the information we share with them for their own purposes, but only if it is anonymized and aggregated, so that it cannot be linked back to any individual.
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or where otherwise permitted by law.
If another company acquires our company or assets, that company may possess the personal information collected by us and will assume the consents and responsibilities regarding your personal information as described in this Policy.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
Please read our Cookie Policy for more information on Cookies and how we use them.
Your Choices
We want you to be satisfied with our use of your information and the communications you receive from us. We are happy to honor your preference requests.
If you feel you hear from us too often or you prefer not to hear from us at all, whether by mail or by email, we are happy to change your preferences. You can make the changes yourself through the My Account section of our website or unsubscribe from our email updates using the link provided in each email. Please keep in mind that if you choose not to receive these promotional emails, you will continue to receive emails from us about recent transactions, including orders and returns.
For Canadian Residents Only: If you are resident of Canada and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) please contact us and we will be happy to assist you.
For E.U. Residents Only: If you are a resident of the European Union and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as your Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the "Right to be Forgotten") please contact us and we will be happy to assist you.
Privacy of Children
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use tendercorp.com with the help of a parent or guardian.
Links to Other Websites
Occasionally we provide links to other websites. These sites operate independently of Adventure Ready Brands and have established their own privacy and security policies. If you choose to navigate to another website through our websites, we strongly encourage you to review the policies of those websites also.
Information Security
Adventure Ready Brands maintains your information securely. It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse, alteration, or unauthorized access of information that we have collected from you or received from a partner. In order to protect it securely, we use a variety of current technologies and processes and are always working to stay current with trends in Information Security. It is our practice to use encryption or hashing whenever we receive or transmit your sensitive information.
Please note: Adventure Ready Brands will never ask you for credit card information over email.
Policy Changes
If our practices change, we will make the necessary changes to this Policy. We will notify you of a change to the Policy by updating
the date above. We encourage you to review it periodically.
Contact Us
For questions or comments related to your privacy, we invite you to contact our customer service department. We're always here to help.
Connect with us!
#AdventureEquipped
© 2020 Adventure Ready Brands. All rights reserved. Terms Of Use & Privacy Policy.
video title
video content
